I'm just... I'm just worried
because I can't see your face.
I think that glass on the angle... yeah.
[Cian] How is it? Better?
Uh, no, I think you made it a bit worse.
I think...
Whoo, I... Yeah, that's perfect.
- [Cian] Yeah?
- Yep.
My name is Andrew.
I'm 27 years old.
I work at Family and Community Services
in Newcastle.
And I want to find a girlfriend
for some love.
[Cian] How would you describe yourself?
Polite, on time,
uh, cute...
organized, as well...
f-f-f-funny.
- [Cian] How are you funny?
- Uh...
Like, sometimes I tend to, um...
make some f-funny jokes,
or different voices, as well.
[Cian] What sort of voices do you do?
Let me think, um...
My name is Bond. James Bond.
- [Cian] Which Bond was that?
- Uh, I think that was Sean Connery.
But, yeah, I'm still getting,
like, used to it.
Like, with the voice,
making it a bit deeper and that.
[Cian] How important would you say
it is to you to find someone special?
I think, to me,
it will be very important
to find someone, uh, for love.
[Cian] What would you rate it,
on a scale of one to ten, how important?
I think ten, actually.
[birds chirping]
[narrator] Andrew's parents
are currently away on holiday...
leaving him in charge of the house.
[Andrew] So, this is actually my bedroom.
This is my number one bear, Angus.
Most of the time,
he normally sits with me.
So, this is Ernie.
He's been my second favorite bear.
I actually got him when I was
about six or seven years old,
from Santa.
And, um also,
the Crocodile Dundee hat, actually.
That's not a knife...
this is a knife.
So, this is my hobby room.
It'll give you a bit more idea
who I am and that, so...
A set of a jigsaw puzzles here.
Most of these old ships here
are very, uh, collective and, uh, fragile.
Here is a collection of my, uh, K'NEX.
So, this is a six-foot clock tower
which I built.
It moves, as well.
So, this is a six-foot, uh, Ferris wheel
that I'm building at the moment,
which is, um, nearly complete.
[Cian] Do you think being
on the autism spectrum
kind of has something to do
with you having
these kind of strong interests in things?
I think so, yes.
[Cian] Sounds like
you like to follow the rules.
Yes. Yeah, rules and procedures,
I'm very strict on those.
[Andrew] Get yourself plenty of ice.
That much will be fine.
My favorite drink is a Sex on the Beach.
- [Cian] And that's a cocktail?
- Yes.
[Andrew] Thirty mils
of the peach schnapps,
then 30 mils of, um, the vodka,
Just stop for a second.
I've made this wrong.
It was supposed to go in this first.
[Cian] Oh, no!
[Andrew] Try again.
Thirty mils of the peach schnapps,
in there... there we go.
You will need 90 mils orange juice.
90 mils of the cranberry juice.
Shake it without the ice
for about ten seconds...
And that's how you make
a Sex on the Beach.
[smacks lips]
Ahh.
Perfection.
[smacks lips] Delicious.
[Cian] Have you ever kissed anyone, Mark?
Like, a girl?
No.
Never.
[Cian] Something you would like to do?
Oh, yes.
I mean, that would...
be quite an experience.
A very huge experience for me.
[narrator] Mark is at the zoo,
waiting for his date to arrive.
I can't wait to see what she's like.
Yeah, I really am excited
and feel really good.
[narrator] Mark is meeting Lauren.
Lauren likes popping Bubble Wrap...
[popping]
...and the sound of the ocean.
[waves crashing]
She hates escalators...
and being chased by chickens.
[clucks]
- Hello.
- [chuckling] Hey.
Nice to meet you, I'm Mark.
Hi, I'm Lauren.
- Nice to meet you, Lauren.
- Hi!
Sorry. I wanted to wave,
but, like, with my crutches...
Oh, no, that's... that's...
that's perfectly all right. That's...
- That's nothing to worry about.
- Yeah.
How are you?
- I'm good, thanks. How are you?
- Looking...
I'm... great. I'm really excited to this.
Yeah, it's so cool.
[Mark chuckles]
- So...
Shall we go in?
- Oh, absolutely.
- Yeah.
Just take your time.
- Yeah, thanks.
- You know, don't want to rush you.
[Lauren] No. It's all right.
[clucking]
So have you visited any places on Earth?
I've only had, like, one major...
um, overseas holiday.
- That was last year.
- Yeah.
So, um, my aunt, who lives in China...
Oh, okay.
Yeah, she was getting married over there.
[Mark] I've always wanted to go to China.
- Let me tell you a bit about myself.
- [Lauren] Yeah.
My favorite animals of all time
are dinosaurs.
When I saw Jurassic Park,
it changed my life, and...
- [Lauren] Oh really?
- Yeah.
- Okay, that's interesting.
- I read all sorts of books on dinosaurs...
- Yeah?
- ...and paleontology, and it...
Okay, cool.
- And I even...
- Like Ross, in Friends.
[Mark] I also love birds,
since birds are the closest
living relatives of dinosaurs.
That's true, yeah.
[trumpets]
- Oh, that's so cute.
- Aww.
It's very sad
there's not many left of them.
[Mark] Yeah, and sadly,
some of them have been
- hunted into extinction by poachers.
- [Lauren] Hmm.
[Mark] During the Ice Age,
the mammoths and the mastodons
were hunted for their meat.
- Oh, yeah.
- You know?
You would think that we would have
learned our lessons, but...
- Yeah.
- ...the tragedy is, we're still doing...
horrible stuff to these beautiful,
intelligent animals
that have the right to live peacefully
on our planet.
I don't know if you've heard,
but they have good memories.
- Ah, yes! Yes, that's right.
- [Lauren] Yeah. I think...
I have no short-term memory.
I have to see people
quite a few times before I remember them.
- [Mark] Oh, okay. Right.
- So...
I'm thinking I should hire an elephant,
I'll teach it to talk...
Yeah. [laughs]
...and then, it can just follow me around,
and it can be my personal memory keeper.
[laughs]
- [Mark] This is the cassowaries.
- [Lauren] They're such pretty animals.
[Mark] Yeah, they're very beautiful,
but they have a really nasty attitude.
They've actually killed people.
- I mean, you see that?
- Really?
Those feet look like very useful
for disemboweling its victims.
Put it this way, they're the closest
as we can get to a raptor dinosaur.
- [low rumble]
- Oh.
[Lauren] Oh, that's a weird noise.
That's not a good noise.
[low rumble]
- Is it gonna start charging?
- I think it's best just to leave them.
Yeah, we'll move on.
- See you, guys.
- See ya.
Oh, she's a very wonderful, charming girl.
She loves animals, and...
really, I'm impressed by her enthusiasm
and her admiration and respect.
[Cian] Do you think
there's any romance in the air?
[chuckles]
That's a bit up in the air at the moment.
I can't say for sure.
But, you know, we'll just have to wait
to see if that spark can be ignited.
[Cian] Would you like for that spark
to be ignited?
Yes. Yes.
I've arranged to see
a penguin-feeding show.
Oh, awesome! Oh, thank you.
- I thought you would love to...
- That's very cool. Yeah.
- I do love penguins.
- So, you want to go and check it out?
Yeah, that'd be great!
- Because I have cerebral palsy...
- [Mark]Yeah.
...my favorite thing about penguins
is that they walk funny.
- Okay.
- And I just love the fact
that there's an animal
that walks like I walk.
[Mark laughs]
These are the little penguins. You have
the opportunity to feed them if you want.
- [Lauren and Mark gasp]
- Absolutely!
[chirping]
Which one of you lucky guys
is gonna get the fish?
Here you go.
Aw, you look so cute!
Waddle, waddle, waddle.
They walk like me!
Is it true that penguins
will choose a partner
and then stick with them for life?
- [Lauren] Is that actually true?
- Exactly.
And they sometimes will select the nest
as to how well the male
has actually built the nest.
- Oh.
- Oh, yes.
So if you're keeping a nice house,
then you'll bring the girls in.
We took a ferry to Manly,
- once upon a time here.
- Oh, yeah? Nice.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
It was beautiful, you know.
Yeah, the Manly ferry's lovely.
- Oh, definitely, and...
- Yeah.
We should do a Manly ferry trip one time.
- That would be great.
- Would be nice.
[Mark] I've always wanted to go
back on the ferry again.
- [Mark chuckles]
- Yeah, so we should, um...
do that one time, maybe.
- Oh, I look forward to that.
- Yeah.
[Cian] Sounded to me like you might
have asked Mark out on a second date.
Um...
I... I may have, yeah. [chuckles]
I... I just...
He was really nice, and I thought...
it'd be cool to catch up again.
Yeah.
Well, thank you for that.
- No, thank you. It was wonderful.
- I hope we meet each other again.
- Yeah, definitely, we'll have to catch up.
- Oh, yes.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
For sure. That was great.
- You take care of yourself, and...
- Thank you. Yes.
Um...
Could I, um, maybe give you a hug?
- Is that all right? Yeah.
- Absolutely. Absolutely.
- Oh.
- [Lauren speaks indistinctly]
- I had...
- I like your shirt.
Thank you.
I had a great time with you, and...
Yeah, it was great.
You know,
I hope we look forward to this again.
Yeah, we'll definitely catch up.
Bye!
[Mark] Bye-bye!
[Cian] It sounded like she asked you
on a second date on the gondola.
Yes.Absolutely.
Absolutely.
- [Cian] That's pretty exciting.
- Yes.
So, I look forward to that, very soon.
Great. Can't wait.
I'm so nervous.
[Cian] Why?
Because I've never done this before.
Hi, my name's Olivia, uh...
I'm 25, and, um...
I have, uh, ASD, Autism Spectrum Disorder.
And I am...
single.
[Cian] How long have you been single for?
Uh...
What's today?
My whole life.
[Cian] What would it mean for you
to find love?
Amazing, I guess.
I don't know. I never thought about it.
[chuckles]
'Cause I didn't think
it was ever going to happen, so...
[Cian] Why don't you think it'll happen?
Ninety-five percent of all people
with autism don't find someone, so...
probably just end up being
another statistic, I guess.
[Cian] Where did you get that figure from?
I don't know. It could be incorrect.
I found it online somewhere.
[Cian] Why do you think so many people
on the spectrum don't find love?
I guess because of
our social difficulties, I suppose.
Oops. [chuckles]
[Cian] Do you ever look at online dating?
No. I've been too scared.
[Cian] Why is it scary?
Because on the internet,
you can be anyone,
and you don't know that... who they are.
I'll show you.
As the meme says, "On the internet,
no one knows you're a cat." [laughs]
I love cats.
This is a Christmas present to myself.
Her name is Duchess.
I call all my cats "Duchess."
I'm not sure why.
[meows]
[purrs]
- [chuckles]
- [meows]
It's supposed to walk,
but this carpet's here, so it's stuck.
- [meows]
- [Cian] Is that cat's name Duchess?
- [Olivia] It doesn't have one.
- [Cian] Why not?
Because I hate that cat.
[Cian] What's it like,
being a girl on the spectrum?
Extremely difficult,
considering that there's no girl criteria.
It's only boy.
So you get... you get assessed
on how male you are.
This has been out all week,
I should fold it.
[narrator] Olivia was diagnosed
with autism when she was 18.
Girls are often diagnosed later than boys
and are sometimes missed
until well into adulthood.
[Cian] What's important to you in life?
Acting. Uh, performing.
That... that is my life.
That's who I am. It's my identity.
I go to Options Theater Company.
It's a, uh, theater company
for people with disabilities.
It's my home. It's my family.
Without them, I don't know where...
I don't know, uh, where I'd be.
It... it changed my life.
- [Olivia] Morning, Stuart.
- Morning, Olivia. Have you got a script?
Ah, no, because I didn't realize I was
gonna be doing my monologue today,
- on a Monday.
- You'll be all right.
I had a hard life, growing up.
So, Olivia playing Oberon.
[Olivia] When I came here,
I felt safe for the first time in my life.
I was finally with people
who understood me.
Where is my puck?
Over the shoulder.
And who get that I was different
to other people, and treated me right.
The trick that's coming in now
is that you're setting the theme up
for Midsummer Night's Dream.
And that's why you're giving her
the flower.
The course of true love
never did run smooth.
Of course it doesn't. [chuckles]
Oh, got some feelings about that?
Have you been in love before?
- [Olivia] I have.
- Have you? Did it break your heart?
- Yes. [laughs]
- [Stuart] Yes.
- Yeah, but you know the feeling, right?
- [Olivia] Yeah.
And that's why... That's why Oberon
is so powerful, so mischievous.
He's scorned.
That's why he's doing this.
Hell hath no fury
like a fairy king scorned.
- Hell hath no fury like a fairy...
- [Olivia laughs]
- Maybe that should be on the poster.
- [laughing]
[Cian] You're jumping around a bit,
Olivia.
Yeah, it's called disability.
I jump around like a ping-pong ball
when I'm happy or excited,
or anxious, or nervous, or stressed.
Um, those the only main triggers
I know of.
- [Olivia laughing]
- [man speaking indistinctly]
[Olivia] At one point,
we thought it was Tourette's.
Another time, we thought
it was chronic motor tic disorder.
Many different theories, but no cigar.
[slight chuckle]
[Cian] And how long
has that been around for?
From the moment I was aware of it.
I was born with it.
[Cian] What does it feel like?
It's a massive build-up
with a pleasant release.
[laughing]
[Cian] So, have you ever been in love?
No.
- [Cian] Have you been in a relationship?
- No.
- [Cian] Have you been on a date?
Yeah, so, at the moment,
with my dating history,
I think it's, uh, pretty poor
at the moment.
[Cian] So, there is no dating history.
Yes.
[narrator] Today, Andrew is preparing
for the arrival of his parents,
who are returning home
from their overseas holiday.
- [Cian] You like things to be clean?
- Oh, yes.
Yeah, they'll be home soon.
Just waiting for them
to come down the street, actually.
[grunts]
[Andrew] Hi!
-Hello, sweetheart. How are you?
- [Andrew] Good.
- We missed you so much!
- I missed you too.
- Ooh, I just lost my sunglasses!
- That's okay.
- Never mind.
[mother] Oh, Andrew, you've done a good
job keeping the house nice and tidy.
[Andrew] Very good.
And here's something that we thought
you'd appreciate, Andrew, and all that.
Oh, thank you.
So, I'll put that with my other, um,
collection of boats, and that.
[Cian] So, Andrew's obviously keen
to find someone special.
What are your thoughts on that?
Oh, we would love him to find someone,
because I know how keen he is himself
to get a girlfriend, and...
and hopefully, one day, a wife.
Because Andrew loves going out.
He loves going out for dinner,
- and he loves going to the movies.
- Yep.
He just doesn't want to do it
with his mum and dad anymore.
[laughter]
Oh, I still do,
but because you're retired...
- [mother] Yes.
- ...you need your quiet time now.
[mother] Yes, plus, you don't want
to spend your life with your mum and dad.
No.
We've always told Andrew,
don't let anybody ever tell you
that you can't do something.
Andrew would always have a crack
and have a go at something.
Very proud of him.
I'd say he's a good boy,
but he's no longer a boy.
- No, I'm a man now.
- That's right. A good young man.
He's got the job
and he's got the license.
- So, now he needs the girlfriend. [laughs]
- That's it.
Andrew's ideal girl would be a girl
that loves jigsaw puzzles and K'NEX.
That would be... that would make it
for him for the rest of his life.
I just hope he finds someone
that he's happy with.
That's all we ever want for Andrew,
is to be happy.
He hasn't said it for a while,
but I have heard Andrew say in the past,
"I wish I was normal."
- [Cian] That must hurt a bit.
- Yeah, it does.
How does it make you feel
when you hear that?
[voice breaking] Pretty... pretty upset.
[Cian] Are you a romantic person?
Yes, I'm a hopeless romantic.
- [Cian] Yeah?
- [Olivia] Hmm.
I love love. I love love songs,
I love rom-coms.
Half my songs on my iPod are roma...
Are, uh, love songs and break-up songs.
[laughs]
[Cian] Have you ever experienced
unrequited love?
When have I not? [chuckles]
I'm usually the, uh, crusher,
not the crushee. [chuckles]
My feelings are never returned, normally.
[Cian] So you've had crushes?
Many.
[Cian] And what... And what happens?
I get very heartbroken. [chuckles]
Because all the guys always...
Always want to hang out with me.
They never want to hold my hand
or date me.
[narrator] Despite her dreams of romance,
Olivia has never been on a date.
Today will be her first.
[Cian] How do you think it'll go today?
Awful. [laughs]
[Cian] What are your concerns?
What are you worried about?
That I have a brain freeze
and I don't know what to say.
Or that it doesn't go well
and I'm not very interesting.
[Cian] It sounds like your worries
are mainly about yourself...
and not about whether
you like the other person.
Aren't they always?
[Cian] Not always. Some people
are very confident in themselves.
I'm not confident in myself.
[keys jangling]
[narrator] It's been half an hour
since Olivia arrived,
and there's still no sign of her date.
This is a bit embarrassing.
Hasn't turned up yet.
I don't wanna be stood up.
[Cian] There he is.
[Olivia] Oh, right.
[narrator] Olivia is meeting Christopher.
He likes the sound of big dogs barking...
[barking]
...and cool breezes.
[breeze softly whistling]
He hates the sound
of slurping spaghetti...
[slurping]
...and sharp radio signals.
[radio static]
- [Christopher] Olivia, right?
- Yeah.
Pleasure to meet you, I'm Christopher.
- You have an accent.
- [slight chuckle]
- Yeah...
- [laughs]
I know, I know.
Everyone immediately thinks I'm American
as soon as they meet me.
- Uh, do you want to get something?
- Yeah.
Uh, hey, can I get a regular latte,
if you got one?
And, uh, anything you want?
The easy street burger combo.
Okay, uh, in that case, uh, no latte.
I'll go straight for a, uh, easy street
beef burger and cheese.
[woman] Thirty-nine dollars.
This actually worked out better,
'cause when I first got here, it was full.
Now there's no one around.
[laughs]
I'm... Again, I'm so sorry
that I waited so long.
I mean, that you waited... [groans]
All right, let me start again.
- I know that feeling. No filter.
- [Christopher] Ah.
Ironically though, it takes me to forever
to get all the thoughts out of my mouth.
I mean, sometimes I immediately think
that I need to, like, go on a script
as soon as I meet someone.
Then as soon as everything happens,
I just feel like a wall
just suddenly slams in there,
then I can't even start to think
until the whole thing's
over and done with.
Sorry, did I speak too fast?
No, I just... I zoned out. That's all.
I have this problem.
Um, I know exactly the feeling.
It takes me forever to try and, uh...
Concentrate.
- Yes.
- [Olivia] Focus.
- Uh-huh.
- [laughs] I have a focusing problem.
- Eh, trial and error.
- Don't you worry, I'm a bundle of nerves.
Cheers to a bundle of nerves, then.
And the birds.
[Olivia laughs]
[dog barks]
You okay?
Um...
Yeah, just got a phobia of big dogs,
that's all.
I used to be a dog groomer.
And trust me, that one's harmless.
Oh, no, I'm not scared of dogs,
just I'm scared of big dogs that jump.
Oh.
[Christopher] Truth be told,
I got pushed into dog grooming
because of what my mother wanted me to do.
I was more an actor and a writer
than anything else.
I'm an actor.
I perform with a theater company
called Options Theater Company.
I would ask for, uh, contact details,
but it's a bit too far for me.
It's okay, you would not be
allowed in anyway.
It's a...
It's a disability theater company.
Don't know whether to take that
as an insult or not.
What is your disability?
'Cause I'm not seeing one.
No offense.
- What does autism look like to you?
- Point taken.
You should take your foot
out of your mouth, sir.
- [woman speaks indistinctly]
- Thank you.
I didn't know I had a foot in my mouth.
Thank you very much.
It is, when you say
you can't see a disability,
because not all disabilities are visible.
And just like that,
I just got proved how blind I am.
[Olivia chuckles]
I normally don't disclose my autism
straight away to people I meet.
I really don't know
how to properly describe myself,
other than just Asperger's syndrome.
That is autism.
I don't know, some people say
it's dyslexic, other people say autism.
At this point, I just want to say,
I'm a madman. Let's just go with that.
My diagnosis is Asperger's.
Hmm. [grunts]
But because Asperger's,
the term doesn't exist anymore,
we're all Autism Spectrum Disorder.
[coughing]
You okay?
I choke on everything. [coughs]
I'm not even sure why, I just do.
[coughs softly]
[Olivia] I like him.
He's a really nice guy.
A bit awkward, but I think
we're both like that, so... [laughs]
I think you just have to take...
you'd have to take some time
to build up the relationship.
[Christopher] I just like
the peace and quiet around here.
[burps] Oh, sorry.
[laughs]
No, actually, that came in the right,
the exact...
That actually came at the right moment.
[laughing]
You're welcome.
[squawking]
Do you want me to start, or...?
Um...
Sure.
I had fun.
And every word that I said to you,
and every word that I listened,
all of it was true.
You're a marvelous woman.
Oh, thank you.
I've never actually been told that before.
I could feel
that you were very genuine, yes.
But I don't see this going any further.
- [Olivia] Mmm.
- Not...
- Not really either, yeah.
- [Christopher] Mmm.
Not because of you or your faults.
No, seriously, look at me.
- I can't, the sun's in my eyes.
- Hang on.
- [laughing]
- How-how's that?
- How's... How's that?
- Yeah. [laughs]
Okay, there we go.
Nothing that you did has put me off.
It's just that whenever I try and look
for someone, I need to find a... spark.
Okay.
Anything...
[Olivia] Ah.
Sorry...
- My jaw just clicked. Ah.
- Oh.
- I actually thought you were about to cry.
- No! My jaw clicked.
[laughs]
It's all right.
Ah.
Well, I definitely want us
to meet again. So, uh...
- Do you want me to, or...?
- Uh...
Whatever you're comfortable with.
Handshake, or...?
Uh...
- Yeah, handshake.
- Okay.
I'm a huggy person,
but I don't know you that well, so...
- Fair enough, fair enough.
- [chuckles]
Ah.
- All right. Well, thank you very much.
- You too.
- Look after yourself.
- I will.
[exhales]
[sighs]
[narrator] Andrew has found out about
a speed dating event being held in town.
It's the first one to be hosted
by a local disability organization.
- Good luck, darling.
- [Andrew] See ya.
- See you later.
- [Andrew] Bye.
[narrator] For Andrew, tonight will be
his very first dating experience.
- Hey, how you doing?
- Hi.
- Milly.
- Milly, Andrew. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, Andrew.
I'm just gonna get you
to sign in real quick.
Yes, excellent.
I have had quite a lot of people
ask me for this event,
because people with these kinds
of differences or disabilities
find it really hard finding other people.
And so, we want everybody
to have the opportunity to fit in.
Thank you all so much
for coming this evening.
I know it's terrifying
and you're probably a bit nervous.
So, if you need any help,
feel free to just stick your hand up
or start screaming.
Whatever you want to do, that's fine.
There are a couple of things
on the table to help out.
So these are questions if you're having
trouble and want something to prompt.
The other thing there
is there are different questions
on each of the numbers.
So you can use the number cards,
or you can use these if you want.
If it doesn't work, it doesn't work.
We're not here to judge,
we're just here to make friends.
[Andrew] Feeling a bit nervous, actually.
Yeah, just I don't want to make
a fool of myself,
don't want to embarrass myself.
Hi, I'm Andrew.
I'm Casey.
- Casey? Nice to meet you.
- Hi, yeah. Nice to meet you.
Yep.
So, um, have you got a job
at the moment, Casey?
Yes, I work at a...
like, the canteen café
at the Newcastle University.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
Yeah. Are you still, um,
living with your parents
- or are you by yourself?
- Yeah. I am.
- Yeah. I still live with my parents...
- Okay.
...but I will be moving out
with my friend soon.
Oh, okay, yeah.
I'm still living with my parents
at the moment, but...
- Yeah.
- [Andrew] Hmm.
Ah, pretty good.
Um...
Any good questions? [chuckles]
No... I'm trying to, yeah,
find some good questions.
Um... [smacks lips]
Have you got a favorite movie?
Favorite movie. Um...
Movies done by M. Night Shyamalan.
- Unbreakable, Glass, and Split.
- Oh, yes. Um...
Yeah, I'm not really, uh,
fussed on those, actually.
- No?
- No.
- What movies do you like?
- Probably, um, James Bond,
um, maybe some of the old,
children's, um, movies,
like Toy Story,
- The Lion King...
- Oh, yeah. Gosh.
Those ones obviously everyone would like,
wouldn't they?
Ah, very good.
[mumbles softly]
[mumbling softly]
[bell ringing]
Well, it's, um, nice meeting you.
- Yeah, it was nice meeting you, too.
- Yep.
- Hi.
I'm Andrew.
I'm Evie.
Hi, nice to meet you.
Nice... Yeah.
Uh...
So, tell me about yourself.
I like to bake cakes,
- Yep.
- I like watching anime...
- ...and I just am obsessed with animals.
Okay. Have you got a favorite animal?
Uh, wolves.
I wanted to work with wolves in Canada.
Okay.
What about you? What do you do?
Um, family, I work actually.
I work for, uh,
Family and Community Services.
- Oh.
- So, it's a, um...
Yeah, a bit of data entry,
uh, stock control,
like, the stationery ordering
and that, yeah.
Um, I need those cards, actually.
Sorry, I'm not really good at talking.
No, no, no, it's okay. I figure we've done
all the good ones, so, um...
Yep.
Uh, let's see. Um...
Ah, no...
If your life was a movie,
which celebrity would you play?
Ah, Kate Hutchins.
I love her.
Okay...
- Oh, yes, now I know who she is. That...
- Yes.
Yeah, um, I don't mind. Um...
Have you heard of, uh, Pierce Brosnan?
Um, James Bond?
- Yeah.
- Yes, he's my favorite,
um, actor, actually.
Um, yeah.
Yeah, do you have a favorite movie?
- Toy Story. [laughs]
- Toy Story?
I know it's childish.
No, no, no, that's okay.
I don't mind Toy Story as well.
Like, all the children's, um, shows,
- like The Lion King, Toy Story...
- Yeah.
- Like the old versions, not the new ones.
- No, no.
'Cause the new ones
are kind of stuffed up.
Yeah. I think probably Toy Story
and Toy Story 2
- would probably be my best, yeah.
- [bell ringing]
- Well, it's nice meeting you.
- Yeah.
- See you again.
- See ya!
[narrator] At the end of the event,
Andrew has chosen
who he would like to see again.
He will only be put in touch
if the other person also chooses him.
I'm actually leaning towards, uh, Evie,
because I could see she was a nice girl,
um, beautiful,
um, her hair was good...
[Cian] You've just gotta hope
she chooses you too, hey?
Yes.
So, fingers crossed. Yep.
- Hey...
- Oh, are you heading off?
Yeah, I'm heading off.
So, it was very nice to meet you.
Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
I'm really awkward with people.
No, that's all right.
It's your first time with me,
you're a bit nervous and that, yeah.
But nice meeting you. See ya Jared!
- See ya!
- [Andrew] Yep.
[knocking]
Hello.
[Cian] How you doing?
Good.
I'm excited. Nervous, excited.
- [Cian] Oh, yeah?
- Yes.
[Cian] In a good way?
Yeah.
It's different than last time.
I feel more prepared than last time.
[grunts]
I am going to wear...
this, and this...
and those shoes.
[narrator] After things didn't work out
on her first date with Christopher,
Olivia is getting ready
to meet someone new.
Olivia is meeting Thomas.
Thomas likes yoga...
[exhales]
...and the sound of chicken wings
being eaten.
[munching]
He doesn't like sirens...
[siren wailing]
...or the itchy feeling of new clothes.
- [Thomas] Hi.
- Hi.
I'm Thomas. [chuckles]
- I'm Olivia.
- Are you a hugger or a shaker?
- Both.
- Oh, well, bring it in.
- I'm very affectionate. [chuckles]
- Me too.
[Thomas laughs]
Oh, I'm Thomas. Sorry.
Do you have an accent?
I like to think I've got
the autism accent.
[Olivia] Oh.
From all the, uh, video games
and movies I watch.
I've got a bit of Polish blood in me.
- [laughs]
- Oh, nice.
What do you like to do for fun?
Play video games.
- Likewise. [laughs]
- Yes.
- [tires screeching]
- I don't know about you,
but I'm sensitive
to sounds and smells...
Not smells, but sounds.
Sounds? Oh, yeah.
And so, sometimes,
when it comes to certain...
- abrupt sounds [snaps fingers] or...
- Yes.
...odors, if you will...
I just, like... I'm like, "Okay, I'm out.
Nope, I'm gone." [laughs]
- Oh, hey.
- [Thomas] Oh!
I thought it'd better to go the soft-drink
route rather than the alcohol route.
- I don't drink, so that's all right.
- That's all right, we'll...
We shall enjoy our fine beverages.
It's orange, like my hair.
How long do you have to spend
with your hair?
Because it looks quite lovely.
I didn't do anything today,
I just brushed it.
- Really? Ah.
- [Olivia] Yes.
See, for me,
I... I go through a vigorous schedule.
I get mousse,
I stylize it,
and then I get, uh, my comb
and I roll it through,
and then I get some hair fiber
and put it through.
Huh? Sorry, I zoned out. Sorry, my bad.
Oh, that's okay, I zone out too.
So, you said you had a movement disorder?
I think one of my, um, students
on the spectrum has that as well.
No, they don't. I guarantee they don't.
Because no one in this world
knows what it is.
- [farts]
- Really?
[laughs]
Happens to the best of us.
[both laugh]
[Olivia] Oh!
- [laughing]
- It's all good.
- It was going so well.
- [both laugh]
That's okay. I... I've already...
I've forgotten it already.
[laughs]
I'm a big fan of voluminous hair,
and she had volume.
And I was like, wow, that's great to see.
Uh, then when we started talking,
and I noticed that she was
as lively as I was,
it's always great to meet someone
who shares your...
types of, you know, engagement.
It's always hard to speak with someone
who is, you know, very shut off.
- Shall we get out of here?
- [Olivia] Yes.
Awesome. I know just a...
A nice little walk along the weir.
And I've got a little surprise for you,
too, okay?
Oh, I'm scared now!
Oh, no, don't worry. Nothing's gonna
come out of the bushes or whatever.
- [laughs]
- [Thomas chuckles]
Did you want me
to put the jumper on for you?
- [Olivia] Yes.
- [Thomas] Awesome.
There you go.
Yeah, just a generally nice person
to be around and...
quite... quite chatty.
I think I've just discovered
what it's like to hear myself for an hour.
[laughs]
- Oh, this is nice.
- Yeah.
Uh, do you go for many walks
along the water?
No, but I always say I'm gonna do it,
but I never do. I need to do it more.
Yeah.
So, I thought a little bit
of a moonlight dance would be nice.
[laughs]
[romantic music plays]
[Olivia] Oh, I can't remember
what this dance was...
I'm not quite sure either.
[both laugh]
[Thomas laughs]
Something wrong?
Please don't do that.
You're making fun of my disability.
No, I wasn't doing that. Sorry.
I was actually dancing
to the, uh... the beat.
- [dog barks]
- That's all. I...
- I... I'm sorry it came off like that.
- [laughs]
I didn't mean to do it.
That's all right.
I got to ask,
how did you feel tonight went?
Um...
[sighs]
You can give me your honest opinion.
It's not that...
You know, I... I can take it.
[laughs]
Ah...
I think we got along pretty well.
We did, yeah.
If you want, um,
we could catch up, maybe in the city?
Uh...
I'd like to talk online first for a while.
That sounds like a good idea.
Very amicable suggestion, indeed.
Well, it was a pleasure to, uh, meet you.
I'll see you around.
- Yep.
- Bye.
Bye.
[Cian] In your family,
you feel like you're the only one
who's still struggling to find someone.
That's it.
It feels, uh, sad,
uh, a bit upset...
Because I want to actually
start my own family, um,
um, as soon as possible, and that.
[Cian] So you feel
you're running out of time?
Yes.
Still nothing.
[narrator] It's the morning
after speed dating,
and Andrew is keen to hear
if he has a match.
[phone chimes]
"Hi, Andrew.
Thank you for attending
our Sen speed dating.
Your matches for the evening
are as follows:
Evie.
The next step is up to you."
[Cian] So that's good news.
Yes, excellent.
- [Cian] How do you feel about that?
- Very excited.
Actually, very pleased with myself.
[Cian] Well done.
- Thank you.
- High five!
Subtitles Diego Moraes(oakislandtk)
www.opensubtitles.org