Will you marry me?
I wanted to tell you something.
One thing that I don't believe in is...
roles.
Or labels.
I do whatever I want.
And what I want you to do is
I want you to stand up.
I'm standing.
So...
throughout this whole thing,
I have been trying to find my soulmate.
I see you as my equal.
And I'm just as strong as you.
So I want to ask you,
Damian Powers,
will you marry me?
I will marry you.
I'll marry you, too!
- I accept.
- I accept, too.
Oh, fuck.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I never expected that.
You scared the shit out of me.
I wanted to surprise you.
You surprised me.
I cannot wait to hold you.
I'm going to break this thing down
in like two seconds.
So, I'm engaged to a man that I've never
seen before and that is so me.
That's something that I would do.
I can't wait to see you, Damian.
You're amazing.
And I look forward...
to spending the rest of my life with you.
Me, too.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
♪ When the world is heartless ♪
♪ When you're in the darkness ♪
♪ Only love can light it up ♪
♪ Light it up, light it up ♪
♪ Light it up, yeah ♪
Today, I feel strongly towards two people,
but I, you know...
Like, I try to avoid
that conflict as well, I guess.
I really want to be married,
but I'm so scared of making
the wrong decision. So...
So, um..
my indecisiveness is killing me
right now.
I know I'm confused in the head.
I don't know what's going on right now.
You told Jessica, "I can see you being
my wife" and all this stuff.
You said that.
But you weren't honest to everyone else
on how you felt about that.
Not just me.
I'm talking about the other two girls.
Yeah, you're right.
Communicate. It sucks.
The conversations fucking blow.
It is fucking awful to be...
The conversation with Jessica
I had yesterday
was the toughest I've had,
ever in my life.
Jessica was conflicted on what was
going on.
She was going back and forth.
And now she's telling me
she's committed to me
and I don't want to be like Barnett:
wishy-washy, uncertain.
Because I know what I want.
And that's Jessica.
Accept the conflict.
Accept it's going to happen,
- and fucking go for it.
- Yeah.
♪ I can still remember
To the night when I surrendered ♪
♪ And we started spinning out of control ♪
I found my person, which is Jessica,
and I've never in my entire life been
able to open up
the way I have with her
and built this connection with her.
I can honestly say I found the woman
that I want to spend
the rest of my life with.
All I hope is that there's
no doubt in her mind
that I'm the man she wants to be with.
- Hello?
- Hey, babe.
Oh, God, hearing your voice...
It's literally the best thing... Oh, man.
The first time I heard your voice,
I just knew.
And there's no words that can ever,
ever, ever...
That I could even describe
to the feeling that you give me
and I promised each and
every day that I will love you...
even when times are tough.
I promise you to be that rock.
I've never been so certain
about something in my life,
and it's so hard
for me to let people in.
And for you, I let you in
and I love every second of it.
Jessica, you have my heart
and there's nobody in this world
that I would rather
spend the rest of my life with.
I want you to picture
this kid from Chicago,
with his heart in his hands,
getting down on one knee,
and Jessica...
I want to ask you...
Will you marry me?
Hello?
Yes.
Of course.
Of course I will.
I want to kiss you, I want to hug you.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, God.
I love you.
I feel like I came into this...
Like, I honestly felt like
God put me here.
I don't know why.
I was like, "This is so weird,
what am I doing?"
But I just want like forever with you.
I don't want this to ever end.
I'm so happy right now.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
My heart's beating out of my chest.
Oh, God. Like, I love you.
And I mean that.
- I love you.
I just got engaged.
I did.
It's been 20 years
of pushing off commitment,
but it was easy to commit
to Mark today.
Love is so blind.
I'm marrying a 24 year old.
Oh, my God.
I tried to push him away,
because that's what I do,
and he wouldn't let me.
And now he is my fiancé.
I'm so excited.
I'm happy. We're good!
I'm excited. Let's do it, like...
- I'm excited, too!
- Whoo!
A lot of people try to say
you should wait until you're 28, 29, 30.
I'm like, but when you find that person,
why wait?
But next time, babe, Jessica,
answer and then cry,
'cause I about had a heart attack
at age 24, so...
My God, I'm...
I wish you could see me right now.
I want you to enjoy the rest of this day
and we got the rest of our lives.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
♪ Feel my, feel my ♪
♪ My adrenaline ♪
♪ It'll never be the same ♪
Being in love with Barnett
is a roller-coaster...
The way he's been interacting
with other girls...
seems so indecisive.
I'm not the only one in this,
so I don't know, you know,
what's in Barnett's mind.
And if it's just feels like such...
high stakes right now.
Even though I feel like I know
who he's wanting to be with,
and it's me,
I don't know that for sure.
I don't even put myself around Amber
at this point.
I just think it's an exhausting thing
to be around.
Honestly, I don't see Barnett
with anyone else.
If he does end up with her,
then I was clearly way off.
Like, way off,
about the kind of person he is
and wants in a wife.
I mean I'm probably, like,
one of the luckiest guys
in the world right now.
Like, I have two freaking amazing people
that are so interested in me.
But how can two people be so sure
and I'm over here, like...
I have no freaking clue.
I have a huge fear of having
this initial spark with someone
and it just fizzling out.
And the intensity of Amber...
like, I'm scared
that it's not going to last.
LC...
I know she'll love me and I know...
it may not be as intense as Amber,
but it could be for a long time
and it won't burn out.
Honestly, I thought about
not proposing to either one.
I don't want to hurt someone
and I know it's going to happen.
And I'm feeling
the fucking pain right now.
It's the...
For sure, the toughest decision
I've ever had to make.
So...
I know I've put you through...
probably one of the hardest experiences
of your life.
This has, uh...
been...
It's been the toughest...
thing I've ever had to do.
I've thought...
everyday and I've...
I've tried to think, you know,
what my future holds
and, you know,
what's the right decision for me.
You know, I have to follow my heart.
It's, it's...
It's not you, LC.
- I literally can't even cry anymore.
- I know.
Like, you just don't have any regard
for what you're doing to people.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have done
this to me.
I would have never...
never...
let you get to this point
if it were me instead of you
in that position.
This is my real life
and my real feelings, and...
I know.
You're not really the person
I thought you were, honestly.
Have a great life.
I'm walking out the door.
♪ You, you, keep me hurting ♪
♪ You, you, keep me yearning ♪
♪ You, you, leave me burning ♪
Why the fuck do guys not ever feel
that sure about me?
Ever?
It's not just here.
Like, I feel like they're always,
like, scared and run.
Like, I don't know what I'm doing
to do that.
Or am I just like...
Like, an unlovable person,
which I don't think that I am.
I don't know what I'm doing wrong.
Clearly, I don't...
I'm not seeing it.
I don't know what's going on.
Like, I'm just like...
having, like...
♪ You, you, keep me hurting ♪
♪ You, you, leave me burning ♪
♪ You, leave me burning ♪
Marriage is a big deal to me
because it's a lifelong commitment.
I've never wanted to get married
unless I felt like it was right.
If I'm going to spend the rest of my life
with this person, I want to make sure...
that it's going to be someone
that I'm going to...
be happy with forever.
Okay.
Amber, um...
you...
are the only one...
that...
makes me feel this burning...
fire in my heart.
But...
Oh, shit.
Amber...
Will you marry me?
Oh...
Oh, my God.
Yes.
- Was that "yes"?
- Yes!
- Yes?
Fuck, okay. Whoo!
Yes. Yes.
♪ Someone's feeling so in love tonight ♪
Oh, fuck.
♪ Someone's falling in love
For the first time ♪
I am not...
ever going to make you doubt that I...
love you, and I'm going to
love you forever.
I knew that I had a spark with LC.
It's just the spark
was stronger with Amber.
Amber...
look at me. Look at me.
Oh, I'm going to make you
the most stressed-out girl in the world.
But you're gonna make me
the happiest man in the world.
I'm already freaking off the walls
right now.
I'm so happy already, so...
God.
I love you.
Oh, shit.
Whoo!
- I already told you I love you, right?
- Yeah.
- I do love you.
Ah!
Yeah.
Phew.
I have insecurities
when it comes to...
how I look.
What will she think of me?
She's such a...
spiritual and loving, kind soul,
that I don't think she's looking
for somebody...
for looks.
She has touched me without touching me.
And...
for the first time in my life,
I think somebody's finally...
seen me without seeing me.
I want to just stare at him.
I just want to process him,
see if he matched
what I thought in my head.
I have no idea what I'm going to do
when I see Damian.
I don't know if I'm going to laugh,
or if I'm going to cry,
or if I'm gonna pass out,
or if I'm gonna throw up,
I have no idea.
Oh, God. Hurry up.
Finally.
Oh, my God, I love you.
Oh my God, you're so strong.
Hi.
Hey.
Mm.
She is stunning.
I mean, she took my breath away.
Her smile was so bright,
her skin tone's so soft
and so fucking...
It's beautiful.
It's so different
and I love different because...
different is beautiful.
Who knew I could get so deep? Ah!
This girl brings out a lot of stuff in me.
You have really pretty eyes.
- Beautiful eyes.
- You have such pretty eyes.
Today I give you me.
I give you all of me.
Wow.
- So, tonight you have a piece of me.
- Good.
Damian.
- Dame.
Dame.
G.
It's interesting.
Because I pictured you, obviously.
I never pictured this.
I love how Damian looks.
I love it. I can stare at him forever.
But my old habits
would have been like "Wait.
Now I'm doubting myself."
'Cause I self-sabotage.
And I didn't do that with Damian.
I am...
so happy.
I can finally let that wall down.
Giannina...
She is fucking beautiful.
I'm sorry for the F-bomb, excuse me,
but she is gorgeous.
I hope she's going back thinking,
"He is a handsome man."
It's crazy that in just four weeks,
Giannina...
is going to be my wife.
I am...
I'm a... I'm a lucky man.
I see you.
Mm.
Barnett has chosen me to be his wife
and he has gotten
a whole crazy handful.
He just...
refused to let me love him!
And he finally gave in.
Today, I get to meet my fiancée.
Oh, it's giving me butterflies.
Roller coaster.
Let's hit that drop, come on.
I'm nervous as hell.
What if she doesn't like me? I don't know.
I haven't,
throughout this entire process,
been able to picture his face.
I haven't been able to fabricate
anything that I feel like
is close enough to who he is.
I'm really hoping for a nice smile
and pretty eyes,
'cause I'm a sucker for both,
but c'est la vie.
Oh, God.
Okay.
Oh, gosh.
- Oh, shit.
- Hi.
Holy fuck.
- Hello.
- Hi!
Oh, God.
Hello. Oh, my gosh.
- Wow.
- Hi.
- Holy shit. Hello.
Hi.
Mm.
- Hi.
- Hey.
How's it going?
Wow.
Did you know the whole time
he looked like that?
Like that's...
That's my fiancé.
All right, I'm going to need
this hand real quick.
I refuse to let you change
your mind again.
I'm gonna stick that on there right now.
Barnett...
frustrates me and he irks my nerves
and he drives me to the ends of insanity,
and...
I fucking love him.
I adore him for it.
Like, I love that he challenges me
and makes me laugh.
And I love the way he makes me feel and...
y'all, I love the way he feels. Oof.
I'm just...
I couldn't be happier right now.
- Oh, my God.
- Don't you dare snort on me.
I got something for you, too.
I had actually picked something out, so...
Is that for me?
- Yes.
- Is that mine?
Hopefully it fits.
Oh, Jesus.
Hell, yeah, this is
the fucking right decision.
Yeah.
Damn, I'm lucky. Shit.
I wasn't nervous at all, but damn.
I was a little nervous.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
- I just want to...
- I'm okay.
Snuggle me real quick.
Don't ever let go.
I'm not going to let you.
They're not going to take you
away from me.
I'm engaged, y'all!
Oh, my God.
I'm engaged.
You're so irritating.
I know I am. I know I am.
I'll always be that way.
Barnett has put me through the wringer.
And I have no doubt
he will probably do it again.
Open the door.
But I am still, and always have been,
up for the challenge
and it feels really good to know
that he is, too.
- Hi.
- Hey.
I never thought
I would come out of this engaged
and definitely never thought I would
come out of this engaged to that...
freaking smokin' hot piece of...
sexiness.
Holy shit.
Finally. Finally.
It's literally the most
freaking beautiful girl I've seen
in my entire life.
Mm.
I'm going to miss you.
Yeah, you are.
Yeah, I am. Yeah, I am.
I'm so glad I didn't let my stupid brain
fuck this up.
See you soon.
♪ Seize the day ♪
♪ Make it never bring you down ♪
♪ You go and do it anyway ♪
Ah!
Oh, God.
Whoo!
Me and my fiancé get to go
on a vacation
and I am ecstatic to get to see what...
this connection is going to be like
in the physical world.
I'm gonna just need to forewarn you guys,
you are not allowed in our hotel room.
Y'all got to stay out.
This experiment for me has
changed my life and I'm 34 years old.
I... thought maybe this was something
that would never happen to me.
It happened. It happened!
Ah.
I'm engaged to someone
10 years younger than me.
I never would have expected
that to happen.
I didn't think about the possibility
of someone...
so much younger
really becoming my everything.
But, yeah, I'm 100%
head-over-heels in love.
Jessica, I love you, baby.
I'm going to make you the happiest woman
in the world,
no matter what conflict is in front of us.
No matter what adversity, obstacle...
You're my person.
Thank you for choosing me.
I couldn't be more thankful
to be with you.
I found the one, and it does not matter
to me at all what he looks like.
If he's a troll, I literally don't care.
I found full-blown love
like I've never experienced before
and it didn't come from seeing someone
across the room who I thought was hot.
It came from...
really connecting with someone
on a deeper level
than I've ever experienced before.
Fuck.
Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, shit.
Fuck.
That laugh.
I wanted to do this in person.
Jessica...
Oh...
Will you marry me?
Yes.
Fuck.
Wow.
Did you see her?
Seriously, like...
holy shit!
Whoo! What?
That's my wife!
That's my wife.
Seeing you right now is...
the best feeling, I...
Is this the image you had in your head?
I don't even know what image
I had in my head.
- Hopefully...
- What was it?
- I don't... I couldn't tell you.
- This is better.
Yeah?
I asked someone earlier
what a 24-year-old looks like.
I didn't know, but you look like normal.
- You look like a grown-ass man.
- Yeah? Is it the beard?
- It's the beard. We'll keep that.
- Okay, phew.
I won't shave it down, I promise.
I wasn't sure with someone
that's much younger than me.
Would it be awkward?
And there was zero awkwardness.
It was just like finally being able to
see this person you've created the deepest
emotional bond of your life with.
Um, I was instantly...
very, very attracted to him.
♪ This is your heart to break ♪
♪ This is your soul to take ♪
♪ This is your move to make ♪
I'm looking forward
to getting married
and creating a family
that we can grow forever.
But I know when we walk out of here,
we're going to be met with
a lot of adversity.
I know friends and family
will have their opinions.
Hey, babe.
- Whoo!
- The person I love may not be
the stereotypical person
that people would choose for me,
but he's my person and I know his soul.
He is the most special person
I've ever met
and age is not a factor for us.
We're not worried about anything
that stands in our way.
Oh, my God.
Holy shit.
♪ This is your move to make ♪
♪ I’m yours to love ♪
In this blind love experiment,
six couples have fallen in love
and gotten engaged, sight unseen.
Hi!
How are you doing? Oh, my God.
Their weddings are just four weeks away.
Now, they've seen each other
for the very first time
and they've come to this tropical paradise
to help turn their emotional connection
into a physical one.
Up until now,
the only thing that's mattered
is who they are on the inside.
Now, their love will be put to the test.
Will their relationships flourish or fail
once they're exposed
to the physical realities
of the material world.
What the couples don't know,
is that they're all gonna be coming
to the same resort...
right here.
They started with love,
an emotional connection.
But... is love enough?
- Thank you.
- Gimme your purse.
Hold this.
It's cool because we're kind of working
like Benjamin Button.
You know, we're working backwards.
I know what he values and I've told him
my deepest fears, everything,
but I still have yet to explore him.
So, I'm excited
about our first night together.
I fell in love with my fiancée
without ever seeing her
and it's, it's, it's... weird.
It's different trying to establish
the emotional
and physical connection together.
When you have a really strong
emotional connection
and then you're bringing
the physical into it,
how do you get them to become one?
- Hmm? No?
- No.
- No?
- I don't know.
Mm.
- Mm-hmm.
- See?
Perfecto.
Yay. Gracias.
Gracias, señor.
- Oh.
- Oh, yeah?
- I was gonna dive in.
Ha ha! Cheers.
Cheers.
The Grand Velas Maya Rivera.
Stunning.
Mm.
It's a dream.
And I am here.
Obviously.
But I can't believe that I'm here.
I just don't want it to ever end.
It doesn't have to.
- No?
- It doesn't have to.
Okay.
What do you think of all this?
I feel like it's a...
fairy tale.
Something tells me
you've always wanted a fairy tale.
Yeah.
Well, it's just because I always grew up
watching movies and reading books
and they always described things like this
and it's always what I wanted
and the fact that I'm...
here...
Unreal, is what it is.
Definitely.
I can not be happier
to be here with anyone else.
You have touched me in more ways
than you can understand.
And...
I love you.
I really do.
I love you more.
Oh, you're gonna make me...
- Pull yourself together!
- I'm working on it.
You get me all emotional.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
That truffle sauce...
- Is that what that is?
- You know what truffle is?
I've heard of chocolate truffles.
You're sexy.
So it's looking pretty romantic in there.
I'm just telling you, it's been 435 days.
435 days since what?
It's just been 435 days.
- Are you talking about...
- Yeah!
So you're talking about 435 days
without sex.
- Yeah.
- And you've counted.
Day 325, I went to the beach
so I can remember how it feels
to have my ass smacked, right?
- By the waves?
- Yeah, by the waves. Exactly.
'Cause it's been a while.
As I told you before, like...
I will move at your pace.
The sex is not... important.
But I do enjoy spending time
with you and getting to know you more.
I want it to be right.
I don't want it to be forced
just because we are engaged.
I just want to tear his clothes off.
I don't know.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Um...
But I'm just not hungry anymore.
- You're not hungry.
- Nope.
- I'm not.
- What about dessert?
I am dessert.
Oh.
This is good.
I hope this isn't hers.
- Happy to be here with you.
- Mm-hmm.
- Me too. Same.
- And you're pretty, too.
- You're pretty.
Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
I am so excited
for my first night with my fiancé.
Just to like, see him
and touch him and smell him
and just cuddle with him.
I do want to have sex with my fiancé,
but, like, not today.
I think we should take things slow.
I love talking to Kenny.
So I feel like we'll, like, stay up
and just talk to one another
and probably just share some kisses
and hold each other, 'cause that's
something we obviously didn't get to do,
up until recently.
Lounge on the... the sofa?
- Whoo!
- Yeah?
Yeah!
Our emotional connection is great.
Our physical attraction is super strong.
So, yeah.
I feel the sex will be,
actually, really good.
He's a really good kisser.
So, I think he has some talent...
elsewhere.
It's so good to see your face.
Like, to literally put like all the sounds
with the expressions now.
- Yeah.
- I can put my arm around you.
- We can count shoulders.
- Nice.
You ever counted shoulders?
- Counted shoulders?
- Yeah, you do one, two, three...
four.
I knew that I was going to accept whatever
she looked like
for exactly who she is.
And who I knew her to be in the pods.
Uh, but, yeah, I'm very much physically
attracted to Kelly.
She's the most wonderful person
that I've ever been around.
Her, you know, personality's infectious,
her laugh's infectious.
Uh, everything about her.
Even holding her hand.
Can I jump on the bed?
So you're already jumping on.
Shoes on and everything, huh?
Expectations for Kelly and I's
first night together
is probably a lot of kissing,
probably a lot of cuddling.
She's so pretty.
Mm. Thank you.
Mm-hmm. You're a pretty, girl.
Mm-hmm.
I'm not asking for kisses.
I know, but you want them.
But I'm a-lookin' for them.
Oh.
Mm.
Being engaged is awesome,
aside from the whole being terrified part.
But I'm definitely hoping
that the physical part with Cameron
matches up with our emotional connection.
This is so sexy this whole...
- Everything.
- ...shebang
Mm.
- Rose petals...
- Mm-hmm.
Hot tub.
You.
Me, you.
I can't think of anything else
that we need.
This is it.
I would love for this to work out
for Cameron and I
because he's everything I've ever wanted
in a husband and a father...
to my future children.
I've never felt like this with any man
and I think that we would have
a wonderful life together.
What more do we need?
I know.
- It's hard not to be a creep.
- I know.
- It's really hard.
- It's hard, I'm trying.
- 'Cause now, it's like, finally...
- Right.
I mean, it's just, you know...
It's just two people in love.
That's what happens.
Yeah.
Yeah, of course I'm excited
to be spending the night with Lauren.
You know, we've been
talking through walls, and...
we really haven't had that, that time to,
you know, be alone with each other.
We're definitely sizing each other up.
Yeah, I like what I see,
to put it very lightly.
This vacation's going to be
one to remember.
- Can I use your toothpaste?
- No.
Of course!
What's mine is yours.
Now we share.
You know, your chest hair is not that bad.
- No?
- I thought it was going to be worse.
You thought it was gonna be worse?
What were you expecting?
I just thought I was going to be like...
super, like...
I don't know, like...
bush.
I've never dated anyone that was white.
This is going to be, like,
a new experience for me.
And my thoughts are that he looks good.
Cameron is very sexy.
He's very attractive.
He has a little swag, so...
I definitely want to jump his bones.
Why is my mind in the gutter?
It's been way too long, y'all. Good lord!
I'm sorry, Mom and Dad. I'm sorry.
I'm an adult. I'm an adult.
Whee!
Mm.
And good night.
This is so beautiful.
Whoo!
Oh, shoot.
Here you go.
Yay.
I am super excited to be with my fiancé
on this romantic getaway,
And I'm so excited to make
a beautiful life together.
Mm. Could you imagine being
the strawberry dipper?
The things you say.
I just tend to say what comes
to mind first.
That's beautiful. I like that about you.
Hello, Mexican police?
- Come get this lady.
- Come get you!
- She's crazy.
- Bye-bye.
They wouldn't touch me.
I had to pick the craziest person
in the house.
You thought I was... I'm not crazy.
Yeah, you're crazy.
I knew that from day one.
- Why? Because I spoke my mind?
- Mm-hmm.
- That's normal, ain't it?
- Mm-mm.
You better be happy you pretty.
- I get away with stuff because I'm pretty?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
I would have been punched it
a long time ago.
- "Punched it"?
- Punched it. Like, "leave."
Okay. Hmm.
Watch your words here.
Come on. Chill out.
Carlton is definitely a different energy
than what we had in the pod.
I don't know if he's nervous
or if he's uncomfortable with something.
You make daddy feel good.
That's why you have that hat on.
You're not slick. Ooh!
You're not slick.
You want one that says "Mommy"?
When I am a mother,
I would love to have one.
I'm gonna get you one that says,
"Do not fucking touch."
No, I would not wear that.
Well...
What about one that says,
"Carlton's wife"?
Okay, I'll do that.
- You would?
- I would do that one,
If I'm your wife.
"If"?
I'm saying,
we still gotta walk down that aisle.
Oh, we're walking down that aisle.
- Okay.
- Ain't no turning back
- Ooh.
- What you gotta figure out?
We gotta move in together.
What do you mean?
I have a big secret to tell Diamond
about my sexuality
and I'm so nervous.
Every moment that I spend with her,
it's in the back of my head.
If I don't roll it out the right way,
it could just turn into a catastrophe
where she just can't deal with it.
I'm gonna get you a pogo stick
so you can hop out of your
feelings right now.
You know what?
You trying to start something.
Whatever.
All right,
so I'm just gonna go to the pool.
No, there is no pool.
I think this conversation's gonna get...
It's over.
Before it gets too deep.
This is our first night together.
I'm excited.
What number is it?
And I'm the happiest girl
in the world. This is us right here.
Ah!
- Yay.
- You ready?
This is the first night
outside of the pod
and it's freaking me out
that I'm engaged right now.
Did I really just do this?
My parents don't know
what's going on right now.
I don't have my phone
so no one knows where I am.
No one knows I'm in Mexico.
It's...
It's crazy and it's tripping me out.
I love hearing the waves crashing
on the beach.
That's my favorite thing
in the whole world.
- I'm thankful.
- Me too.
I love you.
I've always been a very sexual
and romantic and passionate person,
but I have always been missing
that emotional connection.
I believe that now
that I've finally developed
that emotional connection before that,
I think that Jessica and I can really
turn it into...
It's going to feel as though I'm a virgin.
Experiencing something for the first time
with brand new eyes
in a first experience
and I'm excited for it.
Ah! This shirt.
- Love it, love it, love it.
- I'm gonna go shirtless.
- You're going shirtless?
- Yep, going shirtless.
The person I fell in love with
was a voice.
And now here he is in the flesh.
This is him,
and I'm struggling a little bit,
so far, in just...
meshing the two people.
We're about to get
extra friendly here.
All right.
I would say he's not the typical...
guy that I would go for.
My normal type is...
usually a bigger guy.
Um...
Just a bigger guy.
So...
in this experience,
like, I really feel like people
can kinda jump in very quickly,
get into a sexual relationship
and then things don't go well...
and it can be very, very painful.
So my preference is
that we don't go there.
My whole thing is I would never force you
to do anything you don't want to do.
It's me and you.
We started this whole thing just,
again, talking.
I want to get to know you more.
I want you to be you.
I don't want this to be something
that it's not.
The whole reason we're here is
because we took a leap of faith.
- And because of that leap of faith...
- Agreed.
I think, you know...
Whatever I think we both agree on,
yeah, we make it work.
I'm not ready to just,
you know...
jump on him or anything like that,
but I'm kind of excited
because I think part
of this whole experiment is
we've got an emotional bond,
it's not someone I would typically go for
based on looks,
so let's see if we can build off that
and see if that attraction can really grow
and that we can be as deeply seeded
together physically as we are emotionally.
Hey.
Oh.
I don't know.
You might have drank all my champagne.
It's okay.
Just bring the bottle.
Perfect. Yes.
This is our first night
alone together
and there is a little bit of awkwardness
because you know this person
but physically, their body,
their appearance...
Seeing them is totally new to you.
But, that connection,
that fire is just as strong-
as it ever was through a wall.
My fiancé is fine.
Oh!
I'm gonna have such pretty babies, y'all.
You're just going to drink
out of the bottle?
It's what I do.
Like a champ.
- That's my fiancé.
- Yep.
I definitely feel like Amber's
the right girl for me.
And I feel like our physical
relationship is increasing...
our emotional connection.
So, if things happen, they happen,
and I'm not expecting anything,
but we'll see.
- Pretty ring, who got it for you?
- I don't know, some guy.
Some weirdo proposed to me through a wall.
I guess I said yes.
Man, I'm wearing
an engagement ring, too,
- and it's a man version.
- Oh!
If it gets warm, I'm sorry.
Don't you dare!
You're nasty!
I know you.
I can tell when something's upsetting you
and I'm like,
is everything okay?
It's just that feeling, that energy,
I have with you.
I've never seen this side of Carlton
and it really hurts me.
I'm so confused, I don't understand,
it's just so many feelings
are running through me
that I don't even know where to start.
You okay?
- What's on your mind?
- A lot.
With you, I feel like...
I can be myself completely
and I feel like you know when something
is off.
Like, you can sense it.
Like, I really love you,
but it's like certain things
are, like, always in the back of my head.
Certain things like what?
Like the past.
I feel like there was
no possible way you could...
Like, a woman like you...
as perfect as you are,
as beautiful as you are...
Aww...
Hey.
What's wrong?
It's just stuff that we have
to just discuss because...
I feel like...
I've always been in situations where
people have abandoned me
and have, like, rejected me.
First off, you don't have nothing
to worry about.
- Yeah, I do.
- No, you don't.
I do. I have a lot to worry about.
- You have no idea. You have no idea.
- In regards of me.
You could leave me at any moment,
because...
I haven't fully opened up.
What...
What is it that you want
to open up to me about?
I don't feel like you're going to want me
after this information.
What information?
In the past...
I have dated both genders.
What do you mean? Like male and female?
Male and female, yeah.
It's a lot to accept.
I get it. It's okay.
Like, I have my fears. I have...
I have gone through the thought of...
Fuck, you met the love
of your fucking life and now...
My question is, how do you know
I'm the love of your life?
Do you ever feel
like you need to go date...
- No. No.
- ...another man?
No.
That is the biggest misconception
in the world.
The biggest misconception in the world
for men like me, who are honest,
I love...
people for who they are...
at the core.
This has nothing to do with it.
Like, that has never been
the motivating force in my life.
It's a lot to accept.
Yeah.
Like, I'm looking at you right now and...
- I'm listening.
- I feel like your eyes are so blank.
- It's a lot to take in.
- I know. I know.
Fuck!
♪ You slowly vanish
I cannot feel you ♪
♪ Didn't you know? ♪
We were literally
four weeks away from our wedding.
Like, I love Carlton,
but I was not prepared for that.
I...
may leave this earth alone,
but I will leave this earth saying
I was fucking honest.
I didn't fucking deceive nobody
and I did one of the hardest
fucking things that was ever done.
I'm not a hider. What am I hiding for?
Why can I not be myself?
You can be yourself.
I just... I just need time...
to think about this.
It's... I mean,
you just threw a curveball.
I know.
I'm going to...
- Go, just go.
- See you later.
♪ 'Cause you are the tin man ♪
♪ I cannot hear you ♪
♪ Where did you go? ♪
♪ You, you slowly vanish ♪
♪ I cannot feel you ♪
♪ Didn't you know? ♪