[birds chirping]
[narrator] It's been two weeks
since Andrew matched with Evie
after meeting her at a speed dating event,
and he's received some news.
[Andrew] "Hi. I'm really sorry,
but I can't go out with you today,
or for a while.
I'm going through
some very personal stuff.
Sorry for wasting your time. Evie."
Um, I...
And then I replied back, saying, um,
"Hi, Evie. Not a problem.
I totally understand.
Let me know
when you are feeling much better,
if you want to catch up for a coffee."
And then, that's it.
[Cian] It sounded like things
were looking good, and then...
she changed her mind?
Yes.
[Cian] Hi.
Hi, I'm Sharnae, and I'm 21 years old,
and I'm on the spectrum.
[Cian] Describe for me
what your ideal partner would be like.
Caring, amazing,
good-looking.
Jimmy?
Come here.
[giggles] Hello.
Hello.
[whispers] Say your name.
- James.
- Yeah.
You have to look at him.
[inhales deeply]
[exhales]
Hey.
- [Cian] You feeling a bit stressed?
- [whispers] I can't do it. I'm struggling.
I'm here. Look at me.
Hello. We'll do it together.
[Cian] How long have you
known each other?
- Two years. Yeah, two.
- A-Almost three.
Almost three years. Yeah.
[Cian] What did you think
when you first met, Jimmy?
[chuckles] That Sharnae
just thought I was attractive.
[laughing] Yeah. I did.
He's sexy.
I was just, like, "Mum,
there's this hot guy at Job Centre.
I... I'm gonna ask him out."
At that point, I didn't even know
I was on the spectrum.
I just knew I was different.
And Sharnae just...
She just felt similar to me, but...
more like she just knew what I was...
what I was thinking.
Even before I was diagnosed,
she just called me autistic,
- or told everyone I was autistic...
- Yeah. Pretty much.
- ...'cause she believed it so much.
- I did.
[Cian] How old were you
when diagnosed, Jimmy?
Well, I was 20. I'm 21 now.
[Cian] Wow.
I don't know how they missed it.
[Cian] What did you think
when you were diagnosed?
I didn't change.
[both laugh]
[Cian] Why do you think you guys
are compatible?
[whispers] What's that mean?
- [Cian] Are you compatible?
- I hope so. [laughs]
- What does "compatible" mean?
- Compatible means, uh, do we have...
Do we... Do we go well together?
Oh, yeah. Sorry, I didn't know
what that word meant.
Yes, we do. We were made for each other.
I love Sharnae.
I love Jimmy.
- [Jimmy chuckles]
- Ooh.
[Sharnae laughs]
[narrator] It's a special day
for the young couple.
- They're moving in together.
- [Jimmy] I've got you.
- [Jimmy laughs]
- Ooh, thank you.
That's okay.
Yep, and put that in the cupboard.
[Cian] So, there's two knives
and two forks?
- [Sharnae] Yeah, and two plates.
- [Jimmy] Yes.
[Cian] What if you have guests?
- They can bring their own.
- Paper plates.
- [Jimmy laughs] Or bring their own.
- Or bring their own plates and cutlery.
It makes sense.
- It does.
- Yeah.
- [Jimmy] Yeah.
- [Cian] Did Sharnae make that?
[Jimmy] Yeah.
[loud clattering]
- [Jimmy] Jesus Christ. [laughs]
- [Sharnae laughs]
[Cian] Oh, goodness, what's this?
[Sharnae] Oh, wanna see it?
[Jimmy laughing]
[Sharnae laughs]
- [Jimmy] Me and her, printed on a blanket.
- Yeah.
It's really soft, too.
So it's sensory.
We like that kinda stuff,
'cause, yes, we're autistic,
so we like sensory stuff.
[Cian] Why do you put
the eye masks on them?
- I don't know. It's just happy there.
- Yeah.
- It feels right.
- [Sharnae] Yeah.
[Cian] Would you say
this is a big step in your relationship?
- Oh, yes. Yeah, very big.
- Yeah.
Yeah, the biggest so far.
We've been wanting to do it
for ages now, so...
about time we move in together.
- Yeah.
Found a house, perfect.
Yeah.
- [Cian] What's all this, Jimmy?
- [Jimmy] They're all my puzzles.
[whispering indistinctly]
- [Sharnae] He lines it all up.
- [Jimmy] I was making sure it was nice.
[Sharnae] It looks good.
[Cian] How long does it take
to solve a Rubik's Cube?
I like to get sub-one-minute, but...
mostly around the one-minute mark.
[Cian] What is it you love
about doing these puzzles?
[Jimmy] I don't know,
they're kind of just cool.
I originally got the Rubik's Cube
to keep my fingers and hands busy
when I'm anxious,
and I still like them.
- [Cian] Did you just finish it?
- [Jimmy] Yeah.
[Cian] So you like solving things
- in your brain.
- I like to solve things in my brain, yeah.
I see pool like that, as well.
Every rack is a different puzzle.
I c... I see it all
before it all goes down.
They're small, easy puzzles,
but they're still puzzles.
[horn honks]
That must be my pool table.
[Sharnae] Yeah, let's go see it!
- Dun-da-da!
- Okay.
- Come on, hold my hand.
- Come on.
- [Jimmy] Okay.
- [Sharnae] Hello.
- [man] Hi. Where are we going?
- Out the back?
- That way.
- Yeah?
- Yep.
[narrator] To house his prized possession,
Jimmy has set up a marquee
in his backyard.
[Sharnae hums]
Wow, there we go.
[Jimmy] It definitely fits, then.
[Cian] Are you a pro player, Jimmy?
- [Jimmy laughing] Nope.
- Yes.
[Sharnae] You've only been playing pool
for like...
- Two years.
- Yeah.
[Cian] Only two years?
That's not long.
- No, it's not.
- He's already off the rails.
Like, really, really good.
It's possible that it's an obsession.
It's all I can think about, so...
[chuckles]
[Cian] Just Sharnae and pool.
- Yeah.
- [Jimmy] Yeah.
Yep. Indeed.
[Cian] Do you guys remember
your first date?
Yes.
The movies.
[Cian] Did you watch the movie?
- Yeah.
Obviously, it's a cinema.
[both laugh]
Why else would you go to the movies?
Some do it to make out,
that's what he meant.
- Oh, did he?
- Yeah.
- That's what he meant, isn't it?
- No.
- The movies are too good.
- Yeah, it was a good movie.
- We holded hands the whole time...
- Held.
Held hands, thank you.
We hold han... held hands the whole time,
and our arms were getting dead.
And pins and needles, really hurting.
That's what we thought that you do
on first dates.
- I wasn't... I wasn't sure of the protocol.
- Yeah.
I didn't know,
because I'd never been on a date before,
so I thought it was normal too. So...
And then we kissed on the first date,
too, so...
- [Cian] Ooh.
- Yeah.
And then pretty much after that,
he asked me out.
Straight after.
And then we were official.
Isn't that right?
And then Facebook official.
- [laughs]
- [clicks tongue]
[laughs]
- I don't like kissing. Kissing's scary.
- [Sharnae] Don't do tongue.
No, I just don't like it.
It just feels weird.
It's like a lizard.
Stop that.
[Sharnae and Jimmy laughing]
- We do kiss.
- [Jimmy] Oh, nah...
- [Sharnae] Yeah, we do.
- [Jimmy laughing]
We do.
- [Jimmy] Yeah, of course.
- And we hold hands for, like, ten seconds.
- [Jimmy] About.
- About ten.
Five to ten seconds,
- never above ten, but never below five.
- [Sharnae] Yeah.
True that, yeah.
And I'm fine with that.
I don't... I don't really mind.
[Cian] Is intimacy important
in a relationship?
- Intimacy... Intimacy's easy.
- Yeah.
Yeah, it's easy.
[Cian] You don't have to answer.
Have you guys consummated
your relationship?
- [whispers] What's that mean?
- [whispers] I have no idea.
No, I actually do know what it means.
[whispers] Tell me.
[whispers] Guess.
- Yes.
- [chuckles]
Obviously.
[both laugh]
- As I said, it's easy. That stuff's easy.
- Yeah.
[Sharnae laughs]
[Cian] What do you think would be
the biggest challenge for you
in dating, or in a relationship?
Probably, um, that, um... [clicks tongue]
uh, good conversation,
and especially eye contact as well.
[Cian] So, communication?
Uh, yes.
[narrator] To help Andrew
in his search for love,
relationship specialist Jodi Rodgers
has come to work with him
- on his dating skills.
- [knocking]
[Andrew] Hi, I'm Andrew.
Come in.
Nice to meet you. I'm Jodi.
[Andrew] Jodi, nice to meet you.
Come... Come on in.
[Jodi] I absolutely love working
with people on the autism spectrum,
because every single person
is really different,
and the things that they're skilled at,
or their special interests
are really amazing.
I learn something different
about being on the spectrum
from every single person that I meet.
All right, so...
what do you want a girlfriend for?
Just, um, like, um,
start my own family and that.
To be a good father,
and also to keep the family name going
and that...
That's a very traditional way of thinking,
isn't it?
Yes.
So, what's the very first step
for this plan?
It's get a girlfriend.
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
So, when you went on the speed dating,
did you meet anyone?
Um, there... there was this, um, young,
um, lady by the name of Evie.
But then she came down with some, um,
like, personal issues and that.
So, I... I do have the, um, text here.
So...
So, just, um, from that there.
"Hi, I'm really sorry,
but I can't go out with you today,
or for a while."
Oh. How did...
When you get a message like that...
- Yep.
- ...what did you think?
Um, I felt a... a bit down,
and a bit, um, upset and that.
- Yeah.
Do you think that that means there is
a future possibility of going out,
or do you think that means
that's the end of this?
I think maybe there'll be a possibility
in the... the future and that.
But sometimes the words
that come out of our mouth...
- Yeah.
- ...are not really what we're thinking.
When somebody actually says,
"I'm so sorry,
I can't get together...
dot, dot, dot, dot, dot...
for a while,"
what do you think she's thinking?
Mmm. [exhales]
Yeah, that's a really hard question.
This is the... one of the hardest parts
about relationships.
Because...
in her mind,
she was probably thinking to herself,
"I like the look of that Andrew fella."
And then she's thinking,
[smacks lips] "But maybe
he's not boyfriend material."
Okay.
We're strange, humans.
Because rather
than just sending a text saying,
- "Great to get to know you...
- Yeah.
- ...but you are not boyfriend material."
- [Andrew] Hmm.
Instead of saying things
how they really are,
what we do is we try
and make another person feel okay.
[Andrew] Okay. Yep.
And do you think Evie
- wanted to hurt your feelings?
- No, she...
- No way!
- No.
How many dates had you been on
before meeting Evie
- at speed dating?
- None.
- None?!
- No.
It takes a lot of dates
- before you find the right person for you.
- Yes.
- Doesn't it?
- Mmm.
So, that's good practice
- for the next date that's gonna happen.
- Okay.
Do you find body language difficult?
I think, um, when I was in school,
um, yes.
I don't know if I still do, actually.
Okay, so if you wanted to show a girl
that you're really into what she's saying,
what would you do with your face?
That's quite good. I like the...
- the eyes opening up like this.
- Mmm.
If you're going to meet someone,
do you practice?
I think, like, I normally have
like a script in my head,
like what questions
I'm going to ask her and that.
All right, so tell me the questions
when you would go on a...
a date with somebody.
[Andrew] How old are they.
Um, do you work?
Um, do you have any hobbies that you like?
Do you live with your, um, parents?
[Jodi] All right,
so here's your list of questions.
- You take hold of that one.
- Yep.
I'm meeting you for the first time,
so I'm gonna have a list of questions,
too, in my head, that are important.
All right, you start the conversation,
and we'll see if you can actually
keep it going.
Yep. Okay, how old are you?
Twenty-one.
[chuckles] I'm 28 years old.
Um, what do you do for work?
I work with plants.
Um, do you have any hobbies or interests?
I like going to the gym...
and I like doing jigsaw puzzles.
Oh, very good.
I like doing jigsaw puzzles as well.
Um...
Do you live with your parents
or do you live by yourself?
I live by myself.
[Andrew] Okay.
Hmm.
- That's about it.
- [Jodi laughs]
Yeah, I know.
- It's hard, isn't it?
- I know, very hard and that.
Every time...
- there's a question...
- [Andrew] Yep.
[Jodi] ...and we have an answer,
we think to ourselves,
"How could I keep them
- talking about that?"
- Hmm.
Because otherwise, we go on a date,
- we have four questions...
- Yeah.
...the date could be finished
in three minutes.
So let's practice again.
H-How old are you?
I am 21.
[Andrew] Hmm.
- Have you had your 21st birthday yet?
- Excellent! There you go.
Oh, yes,
I had a great 21st birthday party.
- [Andrew] Hmm.
- Three of my friends
went to the movies.
Okay.
When you did go to the movies
with your friends,
what movie did you go and see?
You're good. That's excellent.
I went and saw Fast and the Furious 3.
Oh! Well, that...
I like the Fast and the Furious,
um, movies.
I prefer, uh, number six, actually.
Look at us. What have we just
found out together?
- Very interested in movies.
- How did you show me with your face?
Ah, well done!
Up with your eyebrows. You... I saw it.
So you need to know, you can do this.
Autism isn't stagnant.
People develop, and they change,
and you can see with Andrew
that he's learnt a lot of skill
about social connection with other people.
But it's quite rigid.
Thank you for coming
and, um, teaching me some things.
Andrew needs support to understand
how do we follow and continue
and keep a conversation going
with another person,
so a date doesn't finish
in three and a half seconds
and feel like an interrogation.
And, um, have a good day.
[Jodi] Thank you. See you later.
See you, Jodi.
[Cian] What's the hardest thing
about being on the spectrum?
We do get major anxiety.
We get busy heads.
So sometimes, you know,
like a roller coaster.
Well, it's just...
I think it's just annoying
when other people
- just don't see what I see.
- [Sharnae] Hmm.
[Cian] Is change hard to deal with?
- Change is like a bad holiday.
- [Sharnae] Yeah.
I like holidays,
- but I don't like changes much.
- Change.
- I like planned change.
- [Sharnae] Yeah.
So if you can plan change,
- it's very, very good.
- Easier. And if we...
Yeah, if we get it on the spot,
we're like, "Oh," you know?
- Yeah, it freaks me out.
- Yeah, it freaks us out.
- Sometimes it will...
- [Sharnae] Yeah.
- ...ruin my whole night, even for pool.
- Yeah.
I'll turn up expecting one thing,
and then something might go wrong,
and it will make the whole night
a lot harder. [exhales]
[people chattering]
[narrator] Every Wednesday, Jimmy competes
in a pool competition at his local pub.
This week, a football game is on,
bringing in a bigger crowd than usual.
[people chatting loudly]
[man] He's out! Foot's on the line.
See ya later.
- [Jimmy] I don't think I can do it.
- [Cian] You don't have to, Jimmy.
I just can't.
Maybe in different circumstances.
I just don't... think so.
[Sharnae] You don't think so?
Wanna have a drink, see how you feel?
- I want lemon, lime, and bitters.
- Lemon, lime, and bitters now?
- Yes.
- Yes, okay.
[Cian] Is it that you don't want
to play pool, or...?
I want to play pool, I just don't...
think so.
[Cian] Is it 'cause we're here?
Or is it 'cause there's...
- People.
- [Cian] People you don't know?
I don't know these guys.
If it was like a normal night,
everyone in this...
this whole room, I would know.
But it's not like that at all.
[people cheering]
I don't know if I can do this.
I don't know...
Here, have a drink.
Thanks.
A little bit of freak-out, yeah?
No, I'm having a lot of bit of freak-out.
I know.
[narrator] An hour later,
the pub has quietened down,
and Jimmy's anxiety has eased.
He joins in the pool competition.
Righty-o. Best of three, gentlemen.
- So, that's the game. Thanks.
- Yeah.
- [Sharnae] No need to be nervous.
- [Jimmy] All good.
Righty-o, gentlemen. Best of luck.
Round two.
You good?
- Yeah.
- [Sharnae chuckles]
- Whoa, that was good, wasn't it?
- [exhales]
I like it.
[chuckles]
Thanks.
Well done!
[narrator] In what's becoming
a regular occurrence,
Jimmy has won the pool competition.
- Jimmy, well done.
- Yeah, thanks.
That money's yours.
- Milady... [chuckling]
- Thank you, sir.
[man] See you, guys! See you next time.
[birds chirping]
[Cian] How are you feeling
about the dates you went on?
There were a couple of things
where my filter got in the way.
A couple of things where I was wishing...
Internally wishing I hadn't said it,
and stuff like that.
First dates never really go...
never... never really are good, are they?
[Cian] What's autism
feel like for you?
It's like being in a transparent box.
No one can hear you, no one can...
They can see you,
but they can't interact with you.
You can bang on the wall,
but you can't get out of it,
so it's very lonely being in the box
your entire life.
'Cause no one can get in,
and you can't get out.
And no one can understand you.
[narrator] Olivia hasn't given up
in her search for love.
Today, she's on her way
to meet someone new.
She's meeting Jackson.
Jackson likes origami...
- and the smell of perfume.
- [sniffing]
He hates
- the sound of nails on a blackboard...
- [screeching]
and people slurping their tea.
[slurping]
Hi, I'm Jackson.
I'm Olivia.
Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, too. You look lovely.
Thank you.
- Well, yes.
- Yeah.
Bit hard to sit down on these chairs.
Whereabouts in Central Coast are you from?
- Gosford.
- So am I!
I live in North Gosford.
- Oh, really? No way!
- Yes.
- So close to each other. That's so weird.
- [Jackson] Yeah, it is weird, isn't it?
- What do you like to do?
- I'm a gamer.
What sort of games?
Planning to get
the new Mortal Kombat game.
Oh, that's a good game, yeah.
[both chuckle]
So, like, anything else you do,
like your hobbies, or...?
Um, well, I'm an actor.
- Oh, are you? Wow.
- Yes, with a theater company
- for disabled people.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Oh, cool.
My autism helps me with that a lot.
Also, being very emotional,
which comes from my autism, so...
[chuckles]
My, uh, autism gives me
a very creative side.
- Yeah.
- Uh, but I also have very high thinking,
but I'm, like, slow, uh, motor speeds.
When I was really little, I used to just
go round banging my head on shit,
- just for the fun of it.
- [laughs]
- Would you like to get a drink or coffee?
- I don't drink coffee, I'd like a drink.
- Yeah. I'll go get you one.
- Yeah.
- [Jackson] I'll be back in just a sec.
- Yep.
- [Cian] So, what do you think?
- I'm liking.
I know you've been wanting to hear that
for about three dates now. [laughs]
Here you are.
[quacking]
I wasn't diagnosed till I was 18.
Yeah, about the same for me.
I think 19, maybe.
[Olivia] It's the anniversary next week,
actually,
because I was diagnosed two days
before my 18th birthday.
- Oh, were you?
- Yes.
- Oh, okay.
- [chuckles]
Up until then, I didn't have
any disability help whatsoever.
- You never got any help whatsoever?
- No.
I almost had to repeat, even with support,
so that's amazing.
I do have social difficulties.
Problem is...
they overlooked my symptoms,
because, as a child,
none of my symptoms
were out of place for a child that age.
Oh, really?
Because it presents differently in girls,
and there's no criteria for girls.
- Oh, that's a bit silly.
- [Olivia] Yeah, I know.
Which is why I got... [burps]
Whoa, sorry. [laughs]
Overlooked.
It is. [laughs]
[laughing]
[laughs]
[Jackson] But you're right, now.
You're having some trouble here and there,
and I have some trouble time to time, too,
but, you know,
uh, I think you're very lovely,
and, uh, I don't think there's anything
really that wrong with you.
[Olivia chuckles] Aww.
[Jackson chuckles]
Uh, I've organized a pottery class.
- Would you like to go do that with me?
- Yeah, sure.
- Really?
- Yeah.
All right. Well, good. Let's go!
[Jackson] I think she's very sweet
and she's very cute too.
I like that she can laugh at anything.
That's very nice.
You still a bit cold?
Yeah, but nothing you can do about it.
[chuckles]
Would you like my jacket?
- You sure?
- Yeah, have my jacket.
[Olivia] Thank you.
She's also got pretty red hair.
I can be a bit of a sucker for redheads.
[Jackson] Do you want me
to make something for you or something?
Maybe I can make a controller for you,
since you're so into games.
[laughs] Maybe.
All right.
We're going all Ghost on this date,
with pottery.
[both chuckle]
I can't imagine
how they would've done that scene.
Uh, well, probably would have to do
a lot of retakes.
[Olivia laughs]
- It's a bit creepy, because he's a ghost.
- Yeah.
A bit touchy-feely.
Maybe I would do something like that,
but not on camera, I think.
[both laugh]
That's something couples do in private,
I think.
- Yeah.
- [both laugh]
[Jackson] There you go.
PlayStation controller.
Yay!
[Olivia laughs]
[Olivia] Thank you.
I really enjoyed the day,
and I enjoyed your company.
I just really want
to get to know you more.
- You know?
- Same.
Would you like to do this again?
Yeah, sure!
Can I get your number?
Sure, um...
Um...
- Here.
- [laughs]
Put the game on pause.
- Uh... [laughs]
- [Jackson chuckles]
[phone chimes]
- Okay. Save... Olivia.
- [phone chimes]
Mine can take a picture,
so I'll take a picture of you.
All right.
[camera shutter clicks]
So, um, maybe we'll do this again
some other time, yeah?
Yeah, I'd love to.
All right.
Yeah.
- Let's go.
- [Olivia] Let's go.
[Cian] What do you guys dream about
for your future together?
Well, we wanna get married one day,
but first, we're gonna travel.
I wanna just do all of the things
that Sharnae never thought
she would be able to do.
Breathe in the Gold Coast air.
[excited laughter]
[narrator] Jimmy and Sharnae
are arriving at the Gold Coast
for their first-ever holiday together.
And Jimmy has a surprise in store
for tomorrow.
- [Sharnae] Hey, you!
- Hello.
What are you doing?
[Cian] What have you got planned
for your holiday?
- [Jimmy gasps] We're going to theme parks.
- [squeals] Going on the rides!
We're also going
to a romantic dinner together.
- [Jimmy] Ooh!
- Ooh! [excited humming]
Yeah, we don't usually go
on romantic dates,
because that means
you have to go to restaurants,
and that means you have to go
to places where people are.
We have dinner at our house,
that's romantic.
- Ooh.
- [Sharnae] Ooh.
- [Sharnae] Here to check in.
- Lovely. Yes.
Just a photo ID for check-in.
- There you go.
- [woman] Thank you.
So just reconfirming,
you've booked a one-bedroom
ocean spa apartment for three nights.
- Yeah!
- Fancy.
This is the rules.
It just says don't lose the keys...
- Yeah, we don't do that. We follow rules.
- Perfect.
- So, just both names and signatures.
- We love rules. [chuckles]
1342, right there.
- [Sharnae] Right there.
- Ooh.
[Sharnae chuckles]
[laughing] And we're here.
Oh, my God.
- Whoa, this is pretty cool!
- [laughing] Look at it.
[both] It's got strawberries!
[Sharnae] There's flowers.
- Oh, chocolates!
- Ooh, fancy.
- Are they chocolates or soap?
- No, chocolate.
[Jimmy] Oh, cool.
These spoons
are the wrong way around, though.
- [Sharnae] Holy shit! We got a bath!
- [Jimmy] Oh, look at the bath!
[both laughing]
- Look at that!
- [laughing]
[Sharnae] Oh, my...
- [Jimmy] God!
- [Sharnae] ...God!
- That's so cool.
- Holy shit!
- [Jimmy laughing]
- Whoo!
Wanna go out on the veranda?
- It's raining. Here we go.
- It's gonna be scary.
I can't open it. [grunts]
- I'm so weak.
- [laughs]
- That way.
- Together. Go.
[Jimmy laughs] We're gonna break it.
- [Sharnae] There's a technique.
- What do you do?
[Sharnae] I don't know! No...
You would think,
with our beautiful minds,
we'd be able to open a freaking door.
Wait, this one might open. Nah, key.
[Jimmy] We don't have a key,
but we can go out here. Oh, my Lord!
- [laughing] You can access the roof.
- [Sharnae] Aah!
Oh, my God!
We could die.
Shh! Don't touch it!
Oh, look at the ocean view!
- Isn't it beautiful at nighttime?
- [Jimmy] Isn't it just?
[Sharnae] Wee!
- It's nice and comfy.
- Yeah.
- [Sharnae] Aah! Aah.
- [Jimmy] Mmm.
[Sharnae laughing]
[both laughing]
Aah!
[Sharnae laughing]
- [snorts]
- [Jimmy laughs]
[Sharnae humming]
Yeah.
Uh-oh! They could've died.
Yeah, man.
Gotta wait for the green light.
Rules are rules.
- I'm gonna go on this. Wee!
- Go this way.
Nae!
- [Sharnae] That was fun.
- [Jimmy] You're crazy.
[Jimmy] By the way, have you noticed
we actually hold hands
for longer than five seconds of duration?
- [Cian] True!
- Yes, we are. So sweaty.
- [Cian] When did that change?
- Um...
- I don't know.
- Jimmy's getting used to it more.
- [Cian] Is that a holiday rule?
- Yeah, no.
No, I think I just wanna be...
- as close to Sharnae at all times...
- Yeah.
- 'cause she is my friend.
- I love it. I love you.
- Yuck!
- Can I kiss you?
- No!
- Why?
We're still on camera.
[Sharnae] I don't care about the cameras.
It's just me and you.
[screaming]
[gasps]
[Sharnae laughs]
[Sharnae screams, laughs]
[narrator] It's the afternoon
of Jimmy's planned surprise,
and he's starting to feel the pressure.
- [Cian] What's happening tonight?
- Tonight me and Jimmy
are going on a romantic dinner. [giggles]
So exciting.
I'm getting all ready for it.
This outfit I got from the shops.
It looks like a dress, but it's pants.
[laughs]
- [Cian] Very cute.
- Dress... pants.
Dress... pants.
Hello. You're looking good!
[both chuckle]
Gonna put your jacket on?
- [Cian] He's looking very handsome.
- Yes, very handsome.
[giggles]
Very nice, sexy boy.
[Sharnae] Hmm.
I need navy socks.
- You should get some navy socks.
- Should've got navy socks.
- Idiot.
- Pants are a bit longer.
[inhales through teeth]
[Jimmy] Navy socks.
When you get a navy suit, get navy socks.
[Sharnae] Yeah.
Brown shoes go with navy suits,
not black shoes.
But black socks definitely don't go
with navy suits.
- No.
- [Jimmy] I need navy socks.
- [Sharnae] Yes.
- [Jimmy] Is there a store around here...
Maybe tomorrow.
It's too late.
- Get my bag.
- Look, 'cause if I go like this...
- [Sharnae] Yep, we know.
- [Jimmy] Like that...
- Black socks don't go with...
- [Sharnae] Yep. We'll get navy socks.
[Jimmy, to himself] Idiot.
[Sharnae] Got your cube?
Can you get them ones, please?
Ready to go now?
You gonna do that first?
[Rubik's cube rattling]
- You're a bit... You're upset, aren't you?
- Yes.
[Sharnae inhales deeply]
Navy socks. [exhales]
What do we do now?
Get navy socks.
Yeah, we'll go get navy socks now.
Come on.
[Jimmy] All right, bye.
I'm going to buy navy socks.
I need navy socks.
[door closes]
[Cian] Have any rules for dating?
Be polite, on time,
wear, uh, nice clothes,
uh, good hygiene as well.
Uh, never, uh, use your mobile phone,
especially, uh, viewing Facebook
or social media while dating, as well.
So, yeah.
[narrator] After working
on his dating skills with Jodi,
Andrew is preparing
for his first one-on-one date.
Andrew is meeting Carly.
Carly likes ten-pin bowling...
and smiles.
She hates surprises...
[all] Surprise!
[narrator] ...and the sound
of lawn mowers.
[whirring]
Hi.
- Hi.
- Hi, I'm Andrew.
Nice to meet you, Andrew, I'm Carly.
Nice to meet you too, Carly.
So, have you played lawn bowls before?
- Yeah, I have.
- Okay.
So, if you want to pick a ball up
- and start...
- [straining] Yep.
- Oh.
- What?
[Andrew] That's okay.
Try to remember
- to hold the ball in there...
- Oh, okay.
...and then just roll it like that.
Uh, nice try.
See if you can try
and get down a bit lower,
- and bring your hand like that.
- Oh, yep.
[Andrew] Yep.
Yep, there you go.
Very good!
- So, we'll pick the mat up now...
- Oh, yeah.
...and go up the other end.
[Carly] Yeah.
[Andrew] Very nice, actually.
- [Carly] Hmm.
- [Andrew] Got close to the ball.
So do you, uh,
live with your, uh, parents, Carly?
- I live at home with my parents.
- Yep.
Sorta thing. So what about you...
- I'm still...
- ...Andrew?
[Andrew] Yes, I'm still living
with my parents at the moment.
Okay.
Do you drive a car, have your license?
Um, it's more like, I've got epilepsy.
[Andrew] Oh, I understand.
That one was a bit too fast, actually.
[chuckles]
- Yeah, I think it was.
- Yep.
So, have you been on any,
um, dating, um, history,
gone on a date night or something?
[Carly] Um...
I was with someone before I met you, so...
- Yeah?
- It's kind of been a bit of a...
Like, couple months out of it,
just me trying to...
- Oh, yes.
- Get, like... get back to my usual self.
That's it. I... I understand that.
[inhales sharply]
I was, um... [clicks tongue]
I had someone, uh, before,
and, yeah, went on a date night...
Uh, it was a bit like
- one of those speed dating nights.
- Oh, yeah.
There was... someone matches you, um,
which they did,
but then, after that, um,
that didn't go down too well,
- actually.
- Oh, okay.
[Andrew] Yes.
That's not good.
No, it's a bit disappointing,
but these things happen.
- Yeah.
- [Andrew] Yep.
Ooh, so close.
Just take my jacket off.
It's starting to warm up, actually.
Um, do you want to go...
- have a drink of water, actually...
- Yeah.
- ...before we continue?
- If that's all right.
- [Andrew] Yep.
Mmm.
[exhales]
Very nice.
- Yeah, it is, isn't it?
- Yeah.
[Andrew inhales]
I...
Have I...
Um, okay... Like, am I not making you feel
a bit uncomfortable and that?
- It's real... It's good.
- Yeah.
- It's good.
- Yeah?
Okay.
I'm just, you know...
- trying to be a bit careful.
- Yep.
So, do you s... see yourself one day
starting your own family and that?
Oh. Eventually, when I hit those...
hit the right timing, yes.
Oh, okay.
Because I'm just trying
to get used to the adult...
- life.
- Yeah.
Same thing with me as well.
Like, sometimes I tend to, um, step ahead
or rush things,
but I've gotta step back and think,
"Okay, this takes time" and that.
- Yeah.
- [Andrew] Yep.
So, you ready
to get back into another game?
- Yep.
- Okay.
- [Andrew] So, where I stand here...
- Yeah?
The ball needs to come through...
my legs, actually.
Uh, not bad.
Bit of practice.
Am I making you feel a bit uncomfortable
with all these, um, tips and rules
about lawn bowls?
Yeah, it's good, it's good.
It's just, I'm trying my hardest.
That's okay. It's practice.
- Is that right?
- [Andrew] Uh...
No, other side.
That's it.
[Andrew] Oh.
[Carly laughs]
Now, if I had my hat on,
I would take it off.
Because that would be a great shot.
- It was, wasn't it?
- Yep.
[Andrew]
Oh, here we go, a nice spot out here.
[Carly] Yeah, it is, yeah.
[Andrew exhales]
There we go.
[Andrew inhales]
Well, very good.
Uh...
So, what would be
your ideal dream partner?
Um...
Mine would be, like, for someone to...
you know, sort of care about me.
- Yes.
- Not just, you know...
- use me for other stuff.
- [Andrew] Yep.
It's more like,
trying to be polite to me.
Yeah. Polite to you, um, like, um...
- Understand.
- Yeah.
Especially with your medical condition,
epilepsy.
- Yeah.
- [Andrew] So when the time does happen,
when you do, um, g-get really sick,
or, um, not stable,
you've got someone there to care for you
and that?
Yeah.
What about with you, like...?
I think my dr...
Um, dream partner would be,
yeah, someone nice, um,
someone who has an understanding
with, uh, disability and that, um,
especially with my, um,
intellectual disability and that, um...
Yeah, that's pretty much about it.
- Yeah.
- [Andrew] Hmm.
- Well, thank you, Carly.
- Thank you, Andrew.
- Yep.
- Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you,
and have a safe trip back home.
Yep. Same to you.
- Okay. Bye, Carly.
- See ya.
He seems really polite to me,
which is a good way to have it.
[Cian] Hmm.
But would you like to see him again?
Yeah, possibly. But I'll just
have to check with my parents.
[Cian] Hmm.
[Andrew] It was a really good date.
I probably will see her again,
but, um, probably not at the moment.
Yeah, I might have to give her
a bit of space.
- [Cian] You had some fun, anyway.
- Yes, I did.
[Cian] So, what now? What's next?
Continue, um, going
on those, um, dating, um, sites.
Um, yeah, and just keep trying.
That's the main thing.
- [Cian] Keep going.
- Yes. Never give up.
[birds squawking]
Stop walking so fast, man.
I'm on high heels.
[Sharnae chuckles]
[narrator] With a new pair of navy socks,
Jimmy and Sharnae are heading out
for their special night.
[Sharnae chuckles]
Sharnae thinks we're going to dinner...
but I got a surprise for her instead.
[Cian] How big is the surprise?
Um, life-changing.
[Sharnae] ♪ Singing a song
About one, two, three ♪
- I'm walking up the steps 'cause...
- Because you don't want to fall over?
I'm in high heels.
What the hell?
[piano playing]
- [Jimmy chuckles]
- [Sharnae] What the...
[Sharnae laughs]
♪ You put all your faith in my dreams ♪
♪ You gave me the world that I wanted ♪
♪ What did I do to deserve you? ♪
♪ I waited way too long to say ♪
♪ Everything you mean to me ♪
[inhales]
♪ In case you don't live forever ♪
♪ Let me tell you now ♪
♪ I love you more
Than you ever wrapped your head around ♪
♪ In case you don't live forever ♪
♪ Let me tell you the truth ♪
♪ As long as I'm here as I am ♪
♪ So are you ♪
Sharnae...
will you marry me?
[screaming and laughing]
[sobbing] Yes!
Yes!
Yes! [laughs]
[gasps]
[Sharnae laughing]
Are you okay?
I love you.
- Me too.
- [both laughing]
- I know.
- You did good.
That's pretty. I love it.
- You like it?
- Yeah.
[Sharnae speaks indistinctly]
[laughs]
- [Jimmy laughs]
- You cheeky bugger.
Now you definitely get to spend
the rest of your life with me.
[Sharnae] Yes, forever.
I can't wait to tell the whole world.
[screams]
[yells] I'm engaged!
Whoo!
[inspirational music plays]
Subtitles Diego Moraes(oakislandtk)
www.opensubtitles.org